{
  "groups": {
    "34d4637c0412f2df0030332922d07885": {
      "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
      "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
      "answer": "游때"
    },
    "86d88d9e4e39979f13b822d1643a95f4": {
      "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
      "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
      "answer": "游쥟릖"
    },
    "all": {
      "question_id": "",
      "question": "all",
      "answer": "all"
    },
    "bf1f01da0bfa69d071d64823cefbdf4c": {
      "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
      "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
      "answer": "游"
    },
    "d1bccc85fc14440d4201e4fa2a7a88a2": {
      "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
      "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
      "answer": "游땹"
    },
    "fd212198c64a6510ea26c2c6c14228ba": {
      "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
      "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
      "answer": "游땱"
    }
  },
  "aggregations": {
    "34d4637c0412f2df0030332922d07885": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "游때"
      },
      "count": 1,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "8cec7d6c891fc360bfd61e14b8512896": {
              "answer": "Justice",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "34d4637c0412f2df0030332922d07885": {
              "answer": "游때",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Justice!!!!"
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "86d88d9e4e39979f13b822d1643a95f4": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "游쥟릖"
      },
      "count": 1,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "63ea32f4ca977c1a7ab037224d9d2561": {
              "answer": "Greatness",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "86d88d9e4e39979f13b822d1643a95f4": {
              "answer": "游쥟릖",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Do what you said you'd do!"
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "all": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "",
        "question": "all",
        "answer": "all"
      },
      "count": 7,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "63ea32f4ca977c1a7ab037224d9d2561": {
              "answer": "Greatness",
              "count": 1
            },
            "8afc1f2760cfc2d63b8f0e9ddb1b6f39": {
              "answer": "Economy",
              "count": 4
            },
            "8cec7d6c891fc360bfd61e14b8512896": {
              "answer": "Justice",
              "count": 1
            },
            "ab4b1482cb2ba3f1ee7fd9201c8a1fad": {
              "answer": "War",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "34d4637c0412f2df0030332922d07885": {
              "answer": "游때",
              "count": 1
            },
            "86d88d9e4e39979f13b822d1643a95f4": {
              "answer": "游쥟릖",
              "count": 1
            },
            "bf1f01da0bfa69d071d64823cefbdf4c": {
              "answer": "游",
              "count": 1
            },
            "d1bccc85fc14440d4201e4fa2a7a88a2": {
              "answer": "游땹",
              "count": 3
            },
            "fd212198c64a6510ea26c2c6c14228ba": {
              "answer": "游땱",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Hello there!",
            "Justice!!!!",
            "We need jobs!",
            "Do what you said you'd do!",
            "More jobs please!",
            "Time to go to battle!",
            "Hello there.  That's all."
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "bf1f01da0bfa69d071d64823cefbdf4c": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "游"
      },
      "count": 1,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "8afc1f2760cfc2d63b8f0e9ddb1b6f39": {
              "answer": "Economy",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "bf1f01da0bfa69d071d64823cefbdf4c": {
              "answer": "游",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "More jobs please!"
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "d1bccc85fc14440d4201e4fa2a7a88a2": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "游땹"
      },
      "count": 3,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "8afc1f2760cfc2d63b8f0e9ddb1b6f39": {
              "answer": "Economy",
              "count": 3
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "d1bccc85fc14440d4201e4fa2a7a88a2": {
              "answer": "游땹",
              "count": 3
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Hello there!",
            "We need jobs!",
            "Hello there.  That's all."
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "fd212198c64a6510ea26c2c6c14228ba": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "游땱"
      },
      "count": 1,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "ab4b1482cb2ba3f1ee7fd9201c8a1fad": {
              "answer": "War",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "fd212198c64a6510ea26c2c6c14228ba": {
              "answer": "游땱",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Time to go to battle!"
          ]
        }
      }
    }
  }
}
